and life I say welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother tanzel and
God spake all these words saying I am
the Lord thy God which have brought thee
out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage thou shall have no
other God before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in Earth beneath
or that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for I the Lord thy God am
a jealous God visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children until the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou not take the name of
the Lord thy God in vain for the Lord
will not hold him Guiltless that taketh
his name in vain remember the Sabbath
day to keep it holy six days shall thy
leing do all thy work but the seventh
day is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God
and if thou shall not do any work thou
nor thy son nor thy daughter thy man's
servant nor thy maid servant nor thy
cattle nor thy stranger that us within
thy gates for in six days the Lord made
Heaven and Earth the sea and all that in
them is and rested the seven day
wherefore the Lord bless the Sabbath day
and Hollow it under thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee thou shall not kill thou shall not
commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou not bear false witness against thy
neighbor thou not cover thy neighbor's
house thou not cover thy neighbor's wife
knowest man servant nor his made servant
nor his Ox nor his ass nor anything that
is thy neighbors we read Exodus 21-17
and may the Lord have a blessing to the
reading of his words in Jesus name we
pray amen amen amen so here on question
and answer you can ask us a question and
we'll answer it according to the King
James Bible and if we cannot find the
answer we will seek further counsel to
bring you an answer at a later time the
questions we will not answer are the
vague and the long scripture questions
as well as the questions of debate we
are not here to debate we are here to
spread the true Gospel of Jesus so
please be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as Direct is
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible Bible no other Bibles
or books will be acknowledged on this
program also keep in mind that this is a
live stream and you may begin to send in
your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just asking that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum but
let me introduce to you to family that's
on the panel this evening brother
Jerome Grace and peace brother Julius
good evening everybody brother Dre good
evening brother tanzel good evening
sister Deborah good evening and we have
sister Casey with us as well as a guest
caller and I'm brother Cornell sister
Deborah what is our first question of
the evening yes there are several held
over questions that will be answered
first before getting into tonight's Q&A
so amazing Israelites says the elders
are present in
Revelations when Jesus opened the seals
is this because God called those things
that are not as if they are all right
this is talking about the Book of
Revelations and the elders there brother
Jerome we we know the elders are uh the
24 Elders are in the grave right now
uh but when the seven trumpet um blow
you going to have a u a first
resurrection and they going to take part
in that first resurrection so when you
read about the elders in in the uh new
uh Revelations Book of
Revelations that's just the Lord saying
what you just mentioned he's calling it
as though it is because he know they
going to be in that Resurrection Okay so
um let's go to that Revelations 11th
chapter and we going to read about the
blowing of the seven
trumpet and after that seven you know
during that time you gonna have the
first resurrection okay um pick it up at
verse 15 Read to the 18
tanel and the Seven Angels sounded and
there were great voices in heaven saying
the kingdom of this world become the
kingdom of our Lord and of his Christ
and he shall reign forever and ever and
the 4 and20 Elders which set before God
on their seats fell upon their faces and
worshiped God saying we give thee thanks
oh Lord God Almighty which are and was
and are to come because thou have taken
to thee thy great power and has reigned
and the nations were angry and thy wrath
is come and the time of the Dead that
they should be judged and that thou
should us give them reward to the
servants the prophets and to the Saints
and them that fear thy name small and
great and should us destroy them which
destroy the Earth and you can um also
read in Hebrews the 11th chapter it's a
whole list of
Patriarchs um that's mentioned that
they're going to be made perfect the
same time that you read these 24 Elders
going to be made perfect cuz we know
they coming up in the first resurrection
at the blowing of the seven trumpet
that's when they going to be made
perfect okay and so yeah David is
mentioned Abraham Isaac and Jacob is
mentioned Sarah is mentioned you know in
that 11th chapter and he said they
without us should not be made perfect
and that takes place at the blowing of
the seven
trumpet that's all I got
on right yes sir and everyone on this
panel we all expect to be
also amen we hope that that answered
your question as we continue to move on
to our next one moving on yellow Cal ask
can a
woman fast while on her monthly cycle
and number
two uh she states or he States I
recently became a caregiver for my mom
so I prepare all her meals how can I do
this on the
Sabbath right so first question about
can a woman fast while on her monthly
cycle the answer is yes she can fast
while she is on her monthly cycle and
the second question about you being a
caregiver for your
mom um let's go into um Exodus the 16th
chapter that you're asking about
preparing the meals and how can you do
it on the Sabbath day there's definitely
a way especially when you have a plan at
hand so let's go to Exodus
16 when we get there penzel let's uh do
a little reading a little skipping let's
read um four and five and let's see what
the Lord said here in verse four and
five go
ahead then said the Lord unto Moses
behold I will rain bread from heaven for
you and the people shall go out and
gather a certain rate every day that I
may prove them whether they will walk in
my law or know yeah it shall come to
pass that on the sixth day they shall
prepare that which they bring in and it
shall be twice as much as they gather
daily all right so this is the Lord and
he was telling Moses go out and tell the
people that he gon reain down a certain
rate every day but he said on the sixth
day I want them to gather twice as much
because the next day was going to the
seventh day which they were supposed to
be resting on and not Gathering so you
have to plan on that sixth day as well
for the meals that you want to prepare
for your mom on the Sabbath day Skip
down brother and read 22 and 23 go ahead
and it came to pass that on the sixth
day they gather twice as much bread two
HS for one man and all the rulers of the
congregation came and told Moses uhhuh
and he said unto them this is that which
the Lord hath said tomorrow is the rest
of the holy Sabbath unto the Lord so
bake that which ye will bake today and
see it that ye will see it and that
which remaineth overlay up for you to be
kept until the morning so this is again
that the Lord is talking about the
seventh day is a holy day and it is a
Sabbath to the Lord so he said whatever
it is that you want to bake for that
tomorrow or whatever it is that you need
to boil or prepare or cook for moms you
should be doing that on the six days so
you'll have enough for the seven days so
you won't have to cut your stove on and
use your micro and all that stuff skip
down to verse 25 and go ahead brother
and Moses said eat that today for today
is a Sabbath unto the Lord today you
shall not find it in the
field six days You Shall Gather it but
on the seventh day which is the Sabbath
in it there shall be none
y go ahead and it and it came to pass
and there went out some of the people on
the seventh day for The Gather and they
found
none and the Lord said unto Moses well
how long refuse ye to keep my
Commandments and my
law see for that the Lord have given you
the Sabbath therefore he giveth you on
the sixth day the bread of two days
abide ye every man in his place let no
man go out of his place on the seventh
day so Lord didn't want you to go out
and be gathering bread and looking for
stuff because that's why he said how
long do you refuse to keep my
Commandments because they went out on
the seventh day if they did did it like
the Lord say on the sixth they'd have
been good read the last verse 30 so the
people rested on the seven day and
that's what the Lord want us to do on
that holy day to rest as much as
possible and to prepare for his Sabbath
and that means preparing everything on
the sixth day so you have enough for the
seventh and that's all I
get all right we hope that that answered
your question as we continue to move
right
along moving on Israelite by Blood
Brandon asks are we to work on the
Passover hey Dre are we to work on the
Passover I'd say the Bible doesn't say
anything about you having to work on the
P I mean not work on the Passover but we
should keep the Passover so let's go to
uh Exodus
12 Exodus 12 and pick it up at verse two
read verse two and three and we're gon
to
skip this month shall be unto you the
beginning of month it shall be the first
month of the year to you that is the
month a BB go ahead speak ye unto all
the congregation of Israel saying in the
10th day of this month they shall take
to them every man of lamb according to
the house of their fathers a lamb for an
house give down to verse
five your lamb shall be without blemish
a male of the first year you shall take
it out from the sheep or from the
goats go ahead and ye shall keep it up
unto the 14th day of the same month and
the whole assembly of the congregation
of Israel shall kill it in the evening
now this lamb is representing Christ we
don't do the lamb anym because Christ is
the Lamb of God slain from the
foundation of the world now skip down to
verse 11 verse 11 go ahead and thus
shall ye eat it with your loin girded
your shoes on your feet and your staff
in your hand and you shall eat it in
haste it is the Lord's Passover it is
the Lord's Passover skip down to verse
14 and this day shall be unto you for a
memorial and you shall keep it a feast
to the Lord throughout your generation
and you shall keep it a feast by an
ordinance forever so it is a
memorial that's what the Passover is
verse
16 go ahead and in the first day there
shall be a holy convocation and in the
seventh day there shall be a holy
convocation to you no matter of Works
shall be done in them save that which
every man must eat that only may be done
of you so verse 15 is talking about the
Feast of unleavened bread which is the
uh which is the 15th day the day after
the Passover and the first day you do no
manner of
work save what you must eat that is it
now let's go to ex uh numbers 28 we're
going look at it one more time numbers
28 and read verse 16 to 18 and we going
to
skip go ahead when
you okay and in the 14th day of the
first month is the Passover of the
Lord and in the 15 day of this month is
the feast seven days shall unle bread be
eaten uhhuh in the first day shall be a
holy convocation ye shall do no manner
of Serv our work therein 14th day is the
Passover of the Lord the 15th day of the
month is the Feast of the Lord Feast of
unleavened bread you shall do no manner
of work therein it is letting you know
the first day of the Feast of unleavened
bread but it says nothing about the
Passover in terms of work now skip down
to verse
25 go ahead and on the seven day ye
shall have a holy convocation ye shall
do no Serv our work so on the first day
of unleavened bread and the seventh day
you shall do no no man of work therein
but as far as the uh the Passover it
does not say that you cannot work on
that day uh you can read Leviticus on
your own and that Leviticus 23 and that
will deal with all the Feast of the Lord
and it to tell you about the Passover as
well that's all I
got all right brother thank you for that
hope that answered their question as we
move on to our next one moving on
leaping lamb have several questions
about the memorial and feast days so
leafing lamb ask is Passover one of the
seven feasts is the eighth day one of
the seven feasts of the Lord is
Tabernacles the first day and the seven
day consider one feast or two separate
feasts all right brother Julius we got a
couple of questions TI up in there what
you say
brother come off mute for us
please let's look at what the book say
and let's answer each one according to
the question that's asked number one uh
is the
Passover is the Passover one of the
Seven
Feast of the Lord let's go to Leviticus
the 23rd
chapter T I want you to go to Exodus 12
and hold
it let me show you what the Bible calls
the Passover
Leviticus 231 and2 when you get it
brother go
ahead and the Lord spake unto Moses
saying Speak unto the children of Israel
and say unto them concerning the Feast
of the Lord which ye shall Proclaim to
be holy convocation even these are my
feasts even these are my feasts now when
the Lord calls it a feast sometime he
might call it a holy a solemn assembly
but let's look at what the book says
even these are my feasts watch this
verse four brother go
ahead these are the feasts of the Lord
even holy convocation which ye shall
Proclaim in their seasons in their
Seasons right now come back to the
Passover verse verse five go ahead in
the 14 day of the first month at evening
is the Lord Passover now it is called
the Lord's Passover hold Leviticus 23
and let's go to Exodus 12
Exodus
12 and read verse 11 when you get
it and thus shall ye eat it with your
loins gird your shoes on your feet and
your staff in your hand and ye shall eat
it in haste it is the Lord's Passover so
now on this Passover we eat unle bread
and drink the wine which represent the
body and the blood of Jesus down my
brother to verse 14 what do the Lord
call the
Passover go ahead and this day shall be
unto you for a
memorial and you shall keep it a feast
to the Lord throughout your generation
and you shall keep it a feast by an
ordinance forever now it's a memorial
but what you're feasting on is the bread
and the
wine now with the second question to
that sister Deborah is uh what's the
second question is the eighth day one of
the seven feasts of the Lord yes it is
the seventh Feast of the Lord it is the
seventh Feast of the
Lord now but look at what he call it the
Eighth Day what do he call the eighth
day it is called that last great day
let's look at what Jesus called it let's
go
to St John Chapter 7
St John chapter 7 we'll do a little
reading here I'm sorry about but we need
to break this down and explain it St
John
7 and Dre cover some of this right here
but look at this St John 7 and read to
and we gonna
skip now the Jews Feast of Tabernacle
was at hand so now the Feast of
Tabernacle is a feast okay the Feast of
Tabernacles is the first day is a holy
convocation and that is seven days but
you only require one feast day in
that now
if once you get past
that once you get past that my brother
let's go to Leviticus the 20 back to uh
I'm sorry skip down to verse 37
37 I'm going ahead of myself verse 14
back up read verse 14 go
ahead now about the midst of the feast
Jesus went up into the temple and
Tau and the Jews Marvel saying how
knoweth this man letters have he never
learned now what Feast was this that was
the first day of the Feast of
Tabernacles the Feast of Tabernacle is
seven days you have a holy convocation
on the first day okay now it goes right
into day eight get out way down to verse
37 and read it and look what Jesus
called
it in the last day that great day of the
feast Jesus stood and cried saying if
any man thirst let him come unto me and
drink this is the last Feast of the Year
this is the eth day which is the seven
which is the seventh Feast of the Lord
the seventh Feast of the Lord so now
what's the next question we got Deborah
that is it they want to know is
Tabernacle uh the first day and the
seven day considered one feast or two
Feast it is one Feast that you are that
celebrates one day Tabernacles do that's
the first it's one
Feast cuz then you go to the Eighth Day
on the seventh day the Lord does not
call for a feast on the seventh day
although is not noted it is a 7 Day
Feast but the first day you only have a
holy convocation on
that okay and then it goes right into
the eighth day which is the seventh
Feast of the Lord okay so the Feast of
Tabernacle is seven days but the first
day is a holy convocation of feast but
day seven is not listed as a feast
that's why it goes into the eth day so
the Lord got seven annual Feast
beginning with unleavened bread day one
unleavened bread day seven okay that's
two Feast then he go to the Pentecost
the day of Pentecost that's the third
Feast of the year then it goes into the
day of atonement although it's listed
upon the Feast of the Lord it is a day
where we
fast and we afflict our souls that is
the fifth of the Lord the Tabernacles
into the six but it is the first day of
Tabernacles and then you go into the
Eighth Day which is the seventh Feast of
the Lord Passover is a memorial and the
only thing we eat on that day is the
bread and the wine I know it's confusing
but when you go back and read the
scriptures it straights itself out yeah
so brother Julius could you please
repeat the feast days again because uh
with number four and then five it was
confusing what you said so can you give
me one two three four five six seven
what are those feasts unle bread the
first day unle bread the seventh day
okay that's two days then you got the
third Feast of the year which is the day
of Pentecost that's the third one and
then you have the memorial of blowing
the trumpets which is the fourth one and
then you have the day of atonement which
is the fifth one and then you have
Tabernacles the first day of that feast
and then the eth day which is the
seventh day Feast of the Lord the
seventh Feast of the Lord unle bread
unle
bread uh Pentecost then you have
Memorial blowing the trumpet then you
have day of atonement then you have
Tabernacles and then that that first day
and then you have the eighth day and
that's Seven Feast of the Lord the
Passover is a
memorial all right thank you yes sir
everything has to be done in the seasons
right juli in their seasons and it has
to be done exactly in their season and
they all Point toward
salvation that's correct all right thank
you for that brother as we move on to
our next question next question R Israel
ask in 2 Thessalonians 2 verse 7 who is
the he that will be taken out of the way
is it the comforter or the son of
predition
2 Thessalonians
2:7 who is the he that's going to be
taken out of the way brother
Jerome well
um the he is not uh the comforter that
we refer to as the uh Holy Ghost
um um that's an angel okay um but let's
go read the verse
let's go read it 2 Thessalonians chapter
2 verse
7 for the mystery of iniquity do already
work only he who now leth will let until
he be taken out of the
way now just in case you're not
aware it's two he in that verse and they
both not the same so um the first he
Jesus he the one that's letting this
other he do his thing until he be taken
out of the way and that that other he
that he letting doing what he going to
do that's the son of pedition you
mentioned in your question which is
actually the pope it's going to be the
Pope that uh he going to be in operation
at the time of uh the Great
Tribulation uh so he going to let him do
his thing even during the time of the
Great Tribulation and when that three
and A2 years the Great Tribulation is
over with the first he which is Jesus he
going to take him out of the
way okay so let's uh can you skip up and
read verse four and then we going to
skip back down read that verse four this
is that second he which is the Pope the
son of
pedition who opposeth and exalt himself
above all that is called God or that is
worship so that he as God sth in the
temple of God showing himself that he is
God now I'll read verse
7-9 for the mystery of iniquity do
already work only he who now let will
let until he be taken out of the way
until the pope be taken out of the way
and Jesus going to be the one do it go
ahead and then shall that Wicked be
revealed whom the Lord shall consume
with the spirit of his mouth and shall
destroy with the brightness of his
coming even him who Who coming is after
the working of Satan with all power and
signs and ly wonders okay now I want to
ti ti this God who we know is the pope
all right let's tie this to the
revelations the uh 19th
Chapter and we goingon to read verse one
and two and then we going to
skip go ahead when you get it and after
these things I heard a great voice
of much people in heaven saying
Hallelujah Salvation and Glory and Honor
and power unto the Lord Our God for true
and righteous are his judgment for he
have judged the great which did
corrupt the Earth with her fornication
and have Avenge the blood of his
servants at her
hand skip down to verse 19 read it to 20
and that'll be
it and I saw the Beast and the kings of
the earth and their armies gathered
together together to make war against
him that sat on the horse and against
his Army and the Beast was taken and
with him the false prophet that FSE
Prophet is the pope okay go ahead that W
Miracles before him with which he
deceived them that had received the mark
of the beast and them that worship His
Image these both were cast alive into
the Lake of Fire Burning with Brimstone
that's when he going to be taken out of
way and the Lord have him cast in a lake
of fire that's all I
got right also known as the abomination
of desolation spoken of by Daniel the
Prophet in case you might be just a new
testament Christian only you should go
back and check that out in the Old
Testament in Daniel all right brother
thank you for that light there hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next moving on Stephen Gus asks what
is a heave offering and Covenant of salt
numbers 18 verse 19 is
given and let's go that numbers
18:19 want to know what is the heave
offering as well as the Covenant of
salt and the guess caller would take it
from
there numbers 18 verse
19 yep read all the he offering of the
Holy things with the children of is isra
offer unto the Lord have I given thee
and thy sons and thy daughters with thee
by a statute forever it is a covenant of
salt forever before the Lord unto thee
and to thy sea with
thee okay he he offering he's telling
you well that's one of many offerings
that the that the
priesthood uh
uh
make and the uh uh Covenant of salt mean
permanent I want you to read that 19th
verse again and pay attention to what it
says all the
he okay go
ahead all the heave offerings of the
Holy things with the children of Israel
offer unto the Lord have I given thee
and thy sons and thy daughters with thee
by Statute forever it is a covenant of
salt forever before the Lord unto
thee go
ahead before the Lord unto thee ENT thy
seed with
thee no now and and the Covenant of salt
it mean that's a that's a a promise
forever that mean it don't change there
is telling telling the sons of Levi they
the only ones that can uh uh uh uh make
an offering for the Lord these are the
priest that's why but got Saul uh uh cut
off from being a king because Samuel was
the priest and Saul was afraid of the
Philistines and when Samuel wasn't there
he made an offer and then Samuel told
him you know you made a mistake you
would have been king forever because but
because of that you won't so the uh uh
the offering was supposed to be done by
the Levites and the Levites only and
then the Lord told the Levites that all
of the meat offering uh uh you know when
they made offering to the Lord all of
the meat was for him and is for his seed
forever so the Covenant of salt mean
that it is a covenant that God that God
that made with you forever I give you an
example let's go into 2 Chronicles the
13th chapter and read verse five
read it when you get
there second chronicles 13
and5
right
right go ahead art ye not to know that
the Lord God of Israel gave the kingdom
over Israel to David forever even to him
and to his sons by a covenant of salt
H see see that's why he said made King
David King over Israel
forever and to him in his
seed it is a covenant of salt that mean
forever so now when Jesus let's go and
see what Jesus was called when he came
and see whose Throne he going to set on
let's go into Luke the first
chapter I reading at verse 30
going to read down to
Okay and the angel said unto her fear
not Mary for thou H has found favor with
God and behold thou shall conceive in
thy womb and bring forth a son and shall
call his name Jesus he shall be great
and shall be called the son of the
highest the Lord God shall give unto him
the Throne of his father
David and he shall reign over the house
of Jacob forever and of his kingdom
there shall be no
end now you see when Jesus came he had
to come as a seed of
David and once he get on the throne he
going he said and the Lord God is going
to give him the Throne of his father
David and he is going to rule over the
house of Jacob which is the house of
Israel forever to a covenant of salt of
salt mean that it is an Everlasting
Covenant it will not be
broken all I have to say all right we
hope that answered your question there
as we move on to our next question with
a Time Check Yes the time is
8:05 and cool blue asks is it wrong to
protect yourself from others as if in
fight
all right is it wrong to protect
yourself if you're in a fight um brother
Julius what you
say I say let's go to Ecclesiastes the
thir
chapter Ecclesiastes chapter
3 you know there's a a scripture in the
Bible where joab slew Abner
and the scripture says that uh David
said abna died like a fool his hands
were not
bound D maybe you can pull that
scripture up for me just give me the
scripture and also
um when they came to arrest
Jesus Peter and them had swords on Peter
cut Marcus his ear off although Jesus
told him to put your s back in your
sheep he still had a weapon on him
Ecclesiastes 310 read verse
one to everything there is a season and
a time to every purpose under the
heaven uhhuh a time to be born and a
time to die a time to plant and a time
to pluck up that which is planted uhhuh
A Time to Kill and a time to heal time
to break down and the time to build up
but what about this right here at verse
a time to love and a time to hate a time
of War a time of War a time of war and a
time of peace and a time of Peace so you
have to defend yourself if somebody's
threatening you or to do you bodily harm
and somebody's uh uh they even got it uh
uh they added those into the marriage
vows do you promise to love honor
protect your spouse and you say so help
me God so you have to defend yourself
you have to defend yourself there's
nothing wrong with defending yourself
just let it be justifiable that's all I
got on that if anybody want to
add yeah let go and read what di like a
fool can somebody find it second 2
Samuel
30-33 2 Samuel
3 I wrote over it Dre I'm sorry about
that second Sam
3 2 Samuel
3 pick it up at verse 30 yeah I want you
to pick it up at verse one I want to
show you something in here why these
things happened go
ahead now there was a long war between
the house of Saul and the House of David
but David waxed stronger and stronger
and the house of Saul waxed weaker and
weaker remember what we said there was a
time War now now on down to verse 30 and
go
ahead joab and abashi his brother slew
adner because he had slain their brother
a at gibian in the battle uhuh and David
said to joab and to all the people that
were with him rent your clothes and G
you with sacko and mourn before Abner
and King David himself followed the buer
and they buried Abner in Hebron uhuh and
the King lifted up his voice and wept at
the grave of Abner and all the people
wept and the King lamented over abna and
said die abna as a fool dieth thy hands
were not bound or thy feet put to
feathers as a man fth before wicked men
so fallest thou and all the people wept
again over him so F so FST thou that's
what David said about Abner his hands
was not bound nor his feet put under FEA
feathers he just let somebody can't just
let uh joab came up and killed
him he just try to fight back his hands
was why did the Lord got that there his
hands was not bound nor his feet in
feathers of
chain the man died like a fool because
he didn't defend
himself and I want to throw some in a
reason come like that because AB had
killed his younger brother yep and so
after they had supposed to make peace
then uh uh
uh je said we come to the side my
brother you understand like he going to
talk and and uh uh drew his SW and kill
him I'm should have known I done kill
this guy's brother I ain't going to
trust
him so we trusted him and the GU just
pulled the sword and kill him before and
he didn't try to defend himself that's
why David say you die like a fool so if
you let somebody beat you up and kill
and and hurt you and you don't defend
yourself then you suffering like a fool
that's all I have to
say all right thank you hope that
answered your question there as we
continue to move on to our next moving
on Valencia asked for you to explain
Hosea 11 verse
8 hoseah 11 verse 8 that's the book
right after Daniel so brother Julius
shed some light on that hose 11
and8 you got it
tzel
y read verse
eight but how shall I give thee up
Ephraim how shall I deliver thee Israel
how shall I make thee as Atma how shall
I set thee as zbo
my heart is turned within me my
repenting are kindled
together now what this mean is ephra and
Israel is the same
people okay how should I give thee up o
eph how shall I make the how the Lord
made a covenant with
Israel he said you only have I known of
all the fames of the earth I'mma punish
you but in the end I'm going come and
get you but what happened the Lord is a
uh a a a god of Covenant he keeps his
Covenant but read verse one back read
verse one look what look how why the
Lord chose Israel go ahead when Israel
was a child then I loved him and called
my son out of Egypt that's why he told
Pharaoh Moses you go tell Pharaoh Israel
is my son my firstborn let him go let my
son go so he can serve me if you don't
I'm going kill your firstborn even your
firstborn skip down to verse 8
Now read verse 8 and9 again go ahead how
should I give thee up ephra how should I
deliver thee Israel how shall I make
thee as adma yeah how shall I set thee
as
AO my heart is turned within me my
repent are kle together that's why
everything happened to us happened to us
only because the Lord made a covenant
with Abraham Isaac and Jacob an
Everlasting Covenant but what happened
is we continue to read vers N I will not
execute the fearness of my anger I will
not return to destroy Ephraim for I am
God and not and not man break Covenant
men break Covenant God keeps Covenant go
ahead the Holy One in the midst of thee
and I will not enter into the city give
me chapter 13 just verse
one when Ephraim spake trembling he
exalted himself in Israel uhhuh but when
he offended and H he died so the Lord
made a covenant with Israel gave Israel
his law statutes and Commandments Israel
said all that the Lord said we will
do but he made a
covenant but we didn't keep our part of
the Covenant that's why he had to make
another Covenant say with this with the
same people cuz you not going to give
them up because he made a promise
sisters and brothers now I got one last
place Deuteronomy the 30th chapter tell
you that the Lord is going to keep his
Covenant he called the end like it's
from the beginning and the beginning
like the end Deuteronomy 31 and give me
verse one and
two and this we still waiting on this
here go ahead it shall come to pass when
all these things are come upon thee the
blessing and the curse which I have set
before thee and thou shalt call them to
mind among all the nations whether the
Lord thy God have driven thee yes and
shall return unto the Lord thy God and
shall obey his voice according to all
that I command thee this day uhuh thou
and thy children with all thy heart and
with all thy Soul Now give me verse
three go ahead that the the Lord thy God
will turn thy captivity and have
compassion upon thee and will return and
gather thee from all the nations whether
the Lord thy God have scattered thee so
everything that ever happened to us is
because of what we did sisters and
brothers and the Lord War wers keep my
Commandments have no other God before me
verse
five and the Lord thy God will bring
thee into the land which thy fathers
possessed it yes Thou shalt possess it
and he will do to thee good and multiply
thee above thy fathers because he said
the land that you got I'mma give it to
you and it's G to be your land even
forever verse six and this is it and the
Lord thy God will circumcise thy heart
he going to circumcise
this up here this is the real heart this
pump blood but this is the real heart go
ahead and the Heart of thy seed to love
the Lord thy God with all thy heart and
with all thy soul that thou mayest live
because he is a God he is not man he's a
god of Covenant and he keeps his
promises so that's what that Hosea mean
that's what it means I can't let Israel
go I'm going to hurt him I'm going to
put put him in captivity going to be
sold here and there but I'm going come
and get them in the
end I'm going keep my Covenant I'm not
going to give up on my people who I
promis this Covenant to I hope that
helped yes sir sound like that Covenant
of salt we read about earlier brother
he's not God is not a man that he should
lie that's right all right we hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next one next one Malik Shakur ask
is this
an amount of time you have to fast I'm
not used to it and it's kind of hard can
I fast as long as I can take it or do I
have to fast for a certain amount of
time all right brother Dre share some
light on fasting brother the um the only
scripture that that that tells you that
you must do a fast is on the day of
atonement so let's go and read that
Leviticus
23 and let's pick it up at verse 26
Leviticus 23 and
20 go ahead
brother and the Lord spake unto Moses
saying also on the 10th day of this
seven month there shall be a day of
atonement it shall be a holy convocation
unto you and ye shall flee your souls
and offer an offering made by fire unto
the
Lord you should do no work in that same
day for it is a day of atonement to make
an atonement for you before the Lord
your
God now that day is the day that we fast
because the Lord was afflicted for us he
was afflicted for our sins and we are
called to fast that day and so uh that
was verse 28
right now how long verse 32 go ahead
brother it shall be unto you a Sabbath
of rest and ye shall afflict your souls
in the ninth day of the month at evening
from evening unto evening shall you
celebrate your sabath now notice it says
the ninth day of the month at evening
because the ninth day of the month at
evening is the 10th day so the ninth day
of the month at evening from even onto
even shall you celebrate your Sabbath
which is one day that the Lord is
calling for us to fast on that one day
now there's another scripture that talks
about come things coming out uh certain
struggles we have and they coming out by
fasting and praying
you know our demons or whatever the case
may be coming out by fasting and prayer
but this is one other thing I want us to
look at let's go to uh uh Matthew 6
Matthew 6 and let's pick it up at
verse 16 to
18 go ahead brother when you get it
moreover when ye fast be not as the
hypocrites of a sad continence for they
disfigure their faces that they may
appear unto men to fast but verely I say
unto you they have their
reward but
thou go ahead go ahead y but th when
thou fastest anoint thy head and wash
thy face that thou appear not unto men
to fast but unto th Father which is in
secret and th Father which seeth in
secret shall reward the open yeah in
Daniel 9 and3 Daniel was reading the
book of Jeremiah and he sought the Lord
by fasting and prayer and sackcloth and
sometimes we we pray to the Lord and if
it's a struggle for you to to
fast then you know get you some practice
in and pray the Lord strengthen you that
you may be able to get through that fast
especially on the day of atonement
because that's when the Lord called for
us to do a fast I hope that
help y all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered their
question as we move on to our next one
next question if Joseph is not Jesus
biological father why do Matthew and
Luke both give his
genealogy and why does Matthew cha Trace
Jesus Lage through Solomon while Luke
traces it through Nathan so barbar still
ask why Joseph lineage when Joseph is
not his
father all right guess caller can you
share some light on the
lineage thing is whose son is Nathan
that's one of Solomon's
son that's the first thing but why did
he tras his lineage and why did he call
him Jesus because the Lord said he would
do
it down through his prophecy I start in
Isaiah
7:14 Isaiah 7
and 14
14 therefore the Lord himself shall give
you a sign Behold a virgin shall
conceive and bear a son and shall call
his name
Emmanuel okay the first thing is the
prophecy said he going to a virgin going
to conceive and going to have a son and
should call his name
Emmanuel now let's see when that took
place go to Matthew the 1 chapter and
read verse 23
Matthew 1 and
verse 23 Behold a virgin Shall Behold a
virgin shall be with child and shall
bring forth a son and they should call
his name Emmanuel which is being
interpreted is God With
Us now okay so now when it Virgin uh uh
uh have his
child he going to be called Emmanuel it
mean God Is With Us CU Jesus was God
before he was man so now when he was
born of Mary then God was with us go to
First Timothy 3 and and
17 1 Timothy 3 And1
17 uhhuh you said 1 Timothy
3 uh uhhuh and verse 17
uh because it stop at 16 I think 1
Timothy
3 might want that do you want that 16
and without controversy great is the
mystery of
godliness yeah 3 and 16 I'm sorry read
it and without controversy great is the
mystery of godliness but God was
manifested in the flesh justified in the
spirit seen of angels preaching to the
Gentiles believe on in the world receive
up into
Glory now God was manifest In the Flesh
that meaning God came forth in the flesh
that's why Emmanuel mean God was with us
so how long and now let's go into Luke 3
and
23 read
it and Jesus himself began to be about
30 years of
age being as with being as was supposed
the son of Joseph which was the son of
heli as was what supposed right right
yeah of Joseph you had to be supposed
because remember he was God before he
was man let's go into to Mal Micah the
5th chapter and read verse one and two
now gather thyself in troops oh daughter
of troops he have laid seeds against us
they shall Smite the judge of Israel
with the rod upon the cheek but thou
Bethlehem
eph though thou be a little among the
thousands of Judah yet out of these
shall he come forth unto me that is to
be ruler in Israel whose going forth
have been from of old from
Everlasting so the one that's going to
become rule in Israel
so he's been around for how long from
old to
Everlasting and so Everlasting that mean
he had no beginning and no end right but
who he going to be the judge of Israel
in other words he going to Rule now
let's go into Luke the first chapter
read 30 to
34 that was Luke
1 uhhuh
verse
334 right just get that
real and the angel said unto her fear
not Mary for thou H has found favor with
God and behold thou shal conceive in thy
W and bring forth a son and shall call
his name Jesus he shall be great listen
the reason he called his name he call
him Jesus like the was asked is because
the Lord had the angel called him Jesus
and the angel told Mary that he was
going to be called Jesus that's why he
is called the name of Jesus God had the
angel to tell Mary that now go
ahead he shall be great shall be called
the son of the highest and the Lord God
shall give unto him the Throne of his
father David and he shall reign over the
house of Jacob forever and of his King
going listen he say he's going to give
him the Throne of his father
David now how is David his
father being he said Joseph his father
because he come down through the same
lineage
right go ahead and read and he shall
reign over the house of Jacob forever
and of his kingdom there shall be no
end now what did the Mary say the next
verse then said Mary unto the angel for
how shall this be seen I know not a
man so she wanted to know how can this
be saying that I ain't never had sex in
my life I'm still a virgin it could be
like because God came through
her and she was married to Joseph and
Joseph uh uh uh was supposed to uh uh uh
be Jesus father and Joseph was in the
lineage of
David so how was all that done because
the Lord declared it would be that way
and that's the way it was and that's the
way it is that's all I have to
say yeah that is correct and he even
it's in the scripture saying that and
Joseph laid not with Mary until after
she had her son
Jesus so all right we
hope we hope that answered your question
there as we move on to our next next one
Dr Rock production asks in Genesis 6
verse2 what does it mean the sons of God
saw the daughters of
men brother Jerome what does that mean
in Genesis 6 that the sons of God saw
the daughters of men now let's go take a
look at it Genesis 6 and2
go ahead and read that the sons of God
saw the daughters of men that they were
fair and they took them wives of all
which they
choose and all right it means that the
sons of God looked on the daughters of
men and they look good to them okay they
were attractive that's what it mean they
were Fair okay but these sons of God are
not
Angels not here in this Genesis 6 we not
talking about
J we talking about Genesis 6 these are
men and the reason why you know that is
keep reading it's going to tell you read
verse
three and the Lord said my spirit shall
not always strive with man for that he
also was flesh but yet his days shall be
120 years yeah so he cutting down these
the years of these sons of God which are
he cut it down to
120 we know it's much lower than that
now okay so now uh let's go to Luke the
3 chapter and show that these sons of
God here in this Genesis 6 are actually
Flesh and Blood were flesh and blood men
okay Luke the 3
chapter yeah pick it up at 34 and then
we going to skip
go ahead and read when you get
it which were the son of Jacob which
were the son of Isaac which were the
sons of Abraham which was the son of
thara which was the son of n skip down
we ain't gonna read all of it skip down
to verse 37 and and read it to
38 which was the son of Methuselah which
was the son of Enoch which was the son
of Jered which was the son of Mahal
which was the son of Canaan which was
the son of Enos which was the son of
Seth which was the son of Adam which was
the son of God yeah and that's who these
sons of God were in Genesis the 6th
chapter that's all I
got all right thank you for that we yes
call why don't you catch the lesson
coming up this sabbath
day and you will get a th Thor
understanding of what you're looking for
M yep that'll be in Riverdale this
Saturday at 12
noon all right moving on to our next
question next question Johnny O ask is
there a way for a person to regain one's
faith if they are losing
it is there a way for a person to regain
one's faith if they are losing it well
we don't know exactly where your faith
is at but I would say that while you
going through it it sounds like you
should continue to obey God's
voice and let's go into um Matthew 6
Matthew 6 and let's see what Jesus said
because sometimes it get tough on some
people and they will start wobbling but
you got to do all you can to keep them
on your
wagon Matthew 26
when you get there brother let's pick it
up at that verse
36 okay and then we go skip read that
36 because this is Jesus here when he
was getting ready to pray and then the
disciples fell asleep on them and he
made mention of their flesh but go ahead
Matthew 26 verse 36 then we go skip go
ahead brother then cometh Jesus with
them unto a place called
Geth and said unto the disciples sit ye
here while I go and pray Yonder so he
went so he can go and pray unto the
father he told them to sit there skip
down to verse 40 what happened and he
cometh unto the disciples and findeth
them
asleep and said unto Peter what could ye
not watch with me one hour uhhuh watch
and pray that you enter not into
temptation the spirit indeed deed is
willing but the flesh is weak so you see
the flesh is weak and um if you going
through it hey you have to hold strong
and pray pray and do more prayer and
continue to pray you know because like
the Lord say that the the flesh is weak
but it's the spirit of strong the spirit
of God that's what you have to hold on
to turn over to Galatians 6 Galatians
the 6 chapter
because the Lord don't want you to give
up he said many are the
afflictions of the righteous and others
right Galatians 6 and let's pick it up
at verse four because you are working
out your own salvation here with fear
and trembling verse four go ahead
brother but every but let every man
prove his own work and then shall he
have rejoicing in himself alone and not
in another that's why we say continue to
obey God's voice that will be good
insurance for you skip down to verse
nine and go ahead and let us not be
weary and well-doing for in due Seasons
we shall reap if we faint not because if
you obeying God's voice you are still
doing well while you are going through
your struggles and your times one more
place James two and then we can open it
up because we don't want you to lose
your faith I want you to stay strong and
hold on to the only God that can save
you James 2 and pick it up brother at
that verse 12 James 2 and 12 and we
gonna do some skipping go
ahead so speak ye and so do as they that
shall be judged by the law of Liberty
and so do speak and so do that's why we
say hold on to God continue to obey his
voice skip down to verse 14 go ahead
what doth it profit my brother though a
man say he have faith and have not works
can Faith save him not all by itself you
got to have them Works to go along with
it that's why we say hey keep walking
with God skip down read
17 even so faith if it have not works is
dead being alone skip down and read
20 but will thou but will thou know oh
vain man that faith without works is
dead so continue the good works for God
even though you going through it you
feel as though your faith is wobbling
hey stay with him he can renew your
strength read verse
26 for as the body without the spirit is
dead so faith without works is dead also
yeah so keep working for God even though
it's tough open to the panel anybody
else got scripture one
verse listen
okay go
ahead uh let's go to John 16 and just
one verse 33 Faith your faith is is your
belief and in this world we got a we got
a lot of trials and tribulations but you
got to read this book and put your face
in this book and you got to believe
everything that God got written has and
is going to happen yeah 33 tzel John 16
and33 Look what Jesus said to his
disciples go
ahead these things I have spoken unto
you that in me you might have peace but
in the world ye shall have tribulations
Lord knows there enough drama going on
in the world and then person people
personal life but look what Jesus said
but be of good cheer I overcome the
world and because he overcome the world
we can do it through him through faith
belief in him so that's what the Lord
said be strong and be of good cheer and
read this book and be encouraged hang
around other people but the most
important thing is pray that God give
you a piece uh but and reading get to a
class
man guess
call
well I'm just going to see what Jesus to
said concerning Peter somebody can pull
it up right quick where he said that the
Satan would love to have you that he
might shft you like wheat yeah that what
he told
Peter I want you to find that then see
what Jesus said to him Luke 22 it's go
in Luke 22nd
chapter and pick it up
brother I guess it'll be around verse
31 Luke
[Music]
22 and um yeah
yeah
31 and the Lord said Simon Simon behold
Satan have desired to have you that he
may SI you as wheat but I have prayed
for thee that thy faith fail not and
when thou are converted strengthen thy
Brethren now you know Jesus told this
man that Satan really wants you but I
have that your
faith remain you understand what I'm
saying y now tell this man how you gain
his his keep his faith he just said I
prayed that your faith remain so
according to what this question
said is there a way for a person to
regain one's faith if they losing it my
answer is if if there is I don't know it
that's all I got to
say all
right hope that answered your question
we're gonna move on to our next one
sister going in the new
territory yes we are now into tonight's
Q&A for Wednesday April the 2nd
2025 KY says I had a discussion with a
coworker about the Day Jesus was
crucified he doesn't believe he was
crucified in the middle of the week is
there any other scriptures I can show
him besides Daniel 9 verse
27 all right so this person has a
problem with Jesus being crucified what
you say in the middle of the week Daniel
what 9 verse
27 Daniel 9 and 27 let's go to tanzel
read that right quick and then we can uh
open it up to the
panel and he shall confirm the Covenant
with many for one week and in the midst
of the week he shall call to sacrifice
in the oblations to cease and for the
overspreading of abomination he shall
make it desolate even until the
consummation that the determined shall
be poured upon the
desolate all right the end of that
question was what about the middle of
the week they don't see
that uh they don't believe he was
crucified in the middle of the week so
is there any other scriptures that we
can
read uh to
show uh besides Daniel 9 verse 27 that
was already
read all right to
the Matthew
12 Matthew's 12 and and see what Jesus
tells uh Jesus going to tell you how
many days he going to be in the in in in
the
grave yeah 12 and
38 then certain of the scribes and of
the Pharisees answered saying Master we
will see a sign from thee but he
answered and said unto them and even and
adulterous generation seeketh after a
sign there should no sign be given to it
but the sign of the Prophet Jonas for as
Jonas was three days and three nights in
the Well's belly so shall the son of man
be three days and three nights in the
heart of the
earth so now so you got to find out what
day that Jesus rose on and what day he
rose on that was the last day he was in
the grave so now when the women uh uh uh
uh where where say Jesus uh uh
um proves as it was was uh uh uh d da
and toward the first day of the week
grab
that Matthew
28 and one was that
Mark same book Matthew 28 I think he
said yeah
281 28 and
one in the end of the Sabbath as it
began to da toward the first day of the
week Came Mary Magdalene and the other
Mary to see the
septic okay that's the end of the
Sabbath as it began to do toward the
first day of the week okay when does the
day start somebody go to Genesis and
find out and what the evening in the
morning was the first
day so now so now they went to the supp
car at the end of the s
day as it start the dwn toward the first
the end of the Sabbath the Sabbath day
was over with everybody know that the
Sabbath day is s now go to St John the
20th chapter and read verses 1 and two
yes
sir the first day of the week cometh
Mary Magdalene early when it was yet
dark unto the septic and see the the
stone taken away from the septic
then she runneth and cometh to Simon
Peter and to the other disciples whom
Jesus loved and said unto them they have
taken away the Lord out of the septica
and we know not where they have laid
him okay so now when she got to when
they got to the
graveyard on the first day of the week
that's Sunday while it was still
dark he was gone we read before that
they went at the end of the Sabbath day
the end that means Saturday so that mean
he had to rise before the sun went down
on
Saturday so now you got to count your
days we going to do a backwards count so
Saturday was the third
day and Friday was the second
day and Thursday I mean and and
Thursday uh uh uh uh was the first day
that's cting backwards okay so now he
was in the grave middle of the week is
Wednesday on everybody coun so that mean
that he was crucified and he was put in
the
grave uh Wednesday night he was in there
Thursday night and he was in there
Friday night and then in the daytime he
was in there Thursday he was in there
Friday and he was in there Saturday and
he rose
before Sunday started because they said
as it started the done toward the first
day of the week so that's how you get
your three days Jesus said going to be
in day uh uh in the grade for three days
and three nights the middle of the week
Wednesday night Thursday night and
Friday night Thursday Friday and
Saturday that's your three days and
three nights he had to rise on Saturday
if he rose on Saturday he had to be put
in the grave
Wednesday and Wednesday is the first day
of the
week that's all I have to say anybody
got anything else you
can all right well we hope that that
definitely shares some light on other
scriptures to help you to tie that in
that it was in the midst of the week and
places other than Daniel so we're going
to leave it there we're going to move on
and sister Deborah's time is a ticking
let's open up our next couple of
questions to the panel what is our next
one next one Edward Barber asks why do
some Hebrew Israelites think we are
under the old Covenant and who is wrong
or right about both covenants and
doctrines all right open to the
panel first thing it cannot coexist
under uhuh two Covenant at the same time
so Co down go to Hebrews the 10th
chapter and read verse
one and then skip down to verse uh uh uh
uh four and
continue for the law having a shadow of
good things to come and not the very
image of the things can never with those
sacrifices which they offer year by year
continually make the commas there unto
perfect
verse four for it is not possible that
the blood of bulls and of ghost should
take away
sins wherefore when he
come wherefore when he cometh into the
world he say sacrifice and offering thou
what is not but a body th
prepar see the sacrifice and offer was
under the old Covenant keep
reading and burnt offering and
sacrifices for sin thou H has no
pleasure
but then said I lo I come in the volume
of the book it is written of me to do
thy will oh
God uhuh above when he said sacrifice
and offerings and burnt offerings and
offerings for sin thou wouldest not
neither has pleasure therein which I
offered by the
law I said by the law the law of animal
sacrifice did we read that on the first
verse
then said he lo I come to do thy will oh
God he taketh away the first that he may
establish the second now he taking away
the first what the first Covenant that
he may establish the second you cannot
be under the first Covenant and the
second one which is the New Covenant at
the same time you notice how he said
that he take the away first that he
might establish the second go
ahead by the which we we are Sanctified
through the offering of the body of
Jesus Christ once for
all so now that's when the first
Covenant
started the second Covenant started or
the New Covenant when Jesus died on the
cross
right first that he might establish the
second but keep reading and every priest
stand of daily Ministry and offering
often time the same sacrifices which can
never take away
sins but this man after he had offered
one sacrifice for sins forever sat down
on the right hand of God now skip down
to verse 18 and read
it now where a remission of these is
there is no more offering for
sin so now the first Covenant was
terminated when Jesus died on the cross
that's why the veil of the temple
RI because you you sprinkle the blood of
the first Covenant which is a covenant
of animal sacrifice before the veil so
when Jesus died on the cross the veil of
the temple ripped from top to bottom
there was no more place to sprinkle the
blood therefore there was no more reason
to kill the
animals right that terminated the old
Covenant when he died it did go a day
before because he said he taketh away
the first that he might establish the
second so anybody that say we under the
over Covenant they don't believe in
Jesus that's all I got to say oh that's
simple all right hope that answered your
question there as we move on to our next
one next one miss way says in scripture
Matthew verse uh Matthew
19 verse 12
could I say the Catholic plees are unic
because they marry not and do not have
sex let's go and read that Matthew 19
and 12 and then repeat the question deah
Matthew
19 and keep in mind she asking about can
you say this with the
Catholics go ahead right
for there are some
units which were so born from their
mother's womb and there are some units
which were made units of
men and there be units which have made
themselves units for the kingdom of
Heaven's Sake but he that is able to
receive it let him receive it question
de the question is she says could I say
the Catholic priests are units because
they marry not and do not have
sex sure not only Catholic pre any man
like the Apostle Paul was a
unit
yeah okay we'll leave it right there and
we'll move on to our next question as
time is ticking go ahead yes uh Malicia
cure ask is is there an explanation to
why I always get sleepy when reading the
Bible no matter what time of
day well and word can be very comforting
sometime but um I don't know why that
might be the
case anybody else got an
idea all right right um so hey uh try to
drink a little coffee when you get the
reading in maybe that'll help out all
right let's move on to our next question
next question Jeffrey Meyer asked for
you to Enlighten him on Matthew 16 verse
28 what does Jesus mean about the people
standing there not tasting death
okay so let's go to that um Matthew
16 and let's pick it up at that 27 he's
asking about 28 but it'll kind of read
down because this is talking about the
Lord's return here go ahead brother read
27 and
28 and he wants to know what does it
mean about there'll be some standing
here which shall not of death go ahead
brother for the son of man shall come in
his glory of his father with his angels
and then he shall reward every man
according to his
Works verily I say unto you there be
some standing here which shall not taste
of death till they see the son of man
coming in his
kingdom go right into the
17 all right
yeah
go 17th chapter and it will explain
itself he said there be some standing
here until they see the son of man
coming in his kingdom now when Jesus
made this statement go right into it and
look what happened some days after go
ahead at verse one
10 and after six days Jesus taketh Peter
James and John his brother and bringeth
them up into a high mountain apart so
these are three of his disciples go
ahead and was transfigured before them
and his face did shine as the sun and
his rment was white as the
light they saw the
Lord uh in his glorified body go ahead
and behold there appear unto him Moses
and Elias talking with
them go ahead then answered Peter and
said unto Jesus well Lord it is good for
us to be here but thy will let us make
here three Tabernacles one for thee and
one for Moses and one for
Elias and while he yet spake Behold a
bright Cloud overshadowed them and
behold a voice out of the cloud which
said this is my beloved Son in whom I am
well pleased hear ye
him and when the disciples heard it they
fell on their face and were s afraid
because they saw the end of man and they
saw Jesus in his glorified body and when
they saw Spirit beings in their natural
form shine sisters and brothers that's
why the book said his faith was uh his
uh figure was transformed before them
and his Fai did shine as the Sun so he
showed Peter James and John in his
glorified body and talking to Elijah and
Moses which are dead which will don't
come back until the first resurrection
and they going to have glorified body
also and we want to have them same type
of bodies so 6 days later he took them
into a high mountain and was transformed
before them so they so they saw him in
his glory but they eventually those men
eventually
died now I'm going to
simplify he's simply saying that these
guys that's something here that's not
going to be here is not going to die
until they see me coming in my kingdom
so he went and showed them a vision of
him coming in his kingdom because Moses
and Elijah is going to be in his kingdom
yes sir those guys are s Everyone those
guys there die and the kingdom is not
here that's why he went into the
mountain took them in the mountain and
gave them a vision of the
Kingdom okay yes
sir can we read verse 9 to establish
that read it verse n and as they came
down from the mountain Jesus chared them
saying tell the vision to no man until
the son of man be risen again from the
dead Okay CU there was a vision of of
him in his
kingdom all right all right sister
Deborah this
is very possibly our last question as
time is running out what is the next one
all right most love ass are Africans our
people I'm about to get engaged to an
African from Cameroon West Africa or
does it not matter since everyone is
God's
people so is Africans are
people well the word African is too
broad because Israel came
through uh uh uh the continent of
Africa like Moses was an
Israelite and he married a Ethiopian
woman she was a hamite which uh uh uh
which which uh the Africans
ah so
now you don't know who she came out of
she could be an Israelite or she could
be a
hamite so you don't know who you
marri that's all I got to
say all right let's take one more
question sister Deborah and we will call
it the Eve all right uh Terry Williams
asked
uh and this person has two questions in
Matthew
3:16 is the spirit of God an angel and
in Matthew 4
verse1 is the Angels the holy
spirit so Matthew 3 verse 16 is the
spirit of God an
angel and Matthew 4 4 verse 11 is the
Angels the Holy
Spirit listen right the spirit of God
come in many forms
yes now the word of God is Spirit go to
St John 6 and
6-3 and read
it it is the spirit that Quicken it the
flesh profited nothing the words that I
speak unto you they are spirit and they
are
life he call it so he says words are
called the spirit of God now go into job
21 and start reading at verse
one you get there
you said job
21 uh 21 and one let's see how it
sound but job answered and
said I'm
listening hear diligently my speech and
let this be your
consolation I don't think that's the one
you're looking
for there's not one way is it 19 where
it say the spirit of God in my nostrils
27 27 go ahead 27 and three all the
while my breath is in me and the spirit
of God is in my
nostril now so you have a spirit of God
in your nostrils that's the breath that
you breathe right now go into Hebrew
first chapter and see what he made his
angel
I think you're around four five or uh uh
verse five or
six uh yeah seven
s and of the angels He said who maketh
his Angel spirit and his ministers a
flame of
fire so now when you start talking B
spirit of God you have to be
definitive because we have a uh other
places that tell you the thoughts of the
mind a spirit so when you say the spirit
of God you have to be definitive through
the one that Carri a message he is the
holy spirit which is called the Holy
Ghost which is Gabriel but all his
angels that did not follow Satan they
are spirit and they Are
Holy when people use the word spirit of
God they have to be definitive if not
then then you don't you don't know what
you're talking about that's all I got to
say and we have a lesson on that called
the spirit of God in his many forms
right yeah and that um that that Matthew
3:16 where it talks about and they saw
the spirit of God descending like a dove
and lighting upon
him that's an angel
yep that is indeed an angel and then in
Matthew 4:11 then the devil leaveth him
and behold Angels Came and ministered
unto him and those were the Holy Angels
also
y all right so we hope that
that shed some light on your question
there and we'd like to say sister
Deborah time
check uh the time is not know4 all right
we have ran out of time but we want to
thank everybody from all around the
world who tuned in with us and who sent
in those questions we have fun dining
with you this evening but we like to say
that if you submitted a question and we
didn't get to it please don't resubmit
us sister to Deborah take it and put it
in rotation and we'll deal with that
question next week so until we all come
together again be safe be blessed stay
prayed up and may the Lord have mercy on
us all brother tanzel closes us
out Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our Deb TOs and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus